worldpress.org 2019-06-30

# Worldpress.org - Privacy Policy

About Mission Jobs Advertising Donations Contact Us Privacy Policy Website Traffic Stats 

Worldpress.org takes the privacy of all its users and customers very seriously, and takes great care with user and customer information.

Unless you have voluntarily given us information about yourself we will always ask for your explicit consent if we need to process any personal data about you.

## Security

We take every precaution to protect your personal information. When we ask you to submit sensitive personal financial information, such as your credit card number, we use industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology, making these pages secure.

## Unsolicited E-Mail (SPAM)

Worldpress.org regards SPAM as an annoyance and as a waste of bandwidth. **Under no circumstances will we share or sell your e-mail address with anyone.** If you supply an e-mail address to us, we may contact you by e-mail about your account. Worldpress.org's e-mail newsletters are only sent to readers who request them.

## How Do We Use Your Information?

We may use your personal information to communicate with you, for record keeping purposes, or to improve the usefulness and content of our Web site.

Our Web site may contain links to other Web sites, and you should be aware that we are clearly not responsible for the privacy practices on other sites. We recommend that you individually check the privacy statements of each and every other website that you visit.

Thank you for your interest in Worldpress.org.
